Guide to the Lesbian popular fiction collection,1934-1988.
Lesbian popular fiction collection,1934-1988.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Lesbian popular fiction collection, 1934-1988.
7455
114 v., comprising 1.6 cubic ft.
Novels.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Erotic pulp novels on lesbian subjects, including such themes as seduction, secrecy, and danger.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Erotic pulp novels on lesbian subjects, including such themes as seduction, secrecy, and danger.
SUBJECTS
Subjects:
Lesbians.; Popular literature.
Form and Genre Terms:
Erotica.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Collecting Program: Human Sexuality Collection.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
Books are listed alphabetically by author. Title, publisher, series and series number if applicable (-0- if not), and date are also given.
CONTAINER LIST
- Addams, Kay, Warped Desire, Universal Publishing, B289, 1960 (Box 4)
- Adlon, Arthur, The Odd Kind, Universal Publishing, Beacon Books, B 492F, 1962 (Box 5)
- Aldrich, Ann, We Walk Alone, Fawcett Pub., S 774, 1955 (Box 1)
- Aldrich, Ann, We, Too, Must Love, Fawcett Pub., S 727, 1958 (Box 1)
- Aldrich, Ann, Carol In A Thousand Cities, Fawcett Pub., D 1009, 1960 (Box 1)
- Aldrich, Ann, Den Ensommes Vej, Fawcett Pub. (Danish), -0-, 1966 (Box 1)
- Anonymous, Lesbian Letters No. 1, Stewart Gordon Pub., -0-, 1967 (Box 1)
- Anonymous, Lesbian Letters No. 2, Stewart Gordon Pub., -0-, 1967 (Box 2)
- Anonymous, Lion-Taming Tigresses, Star Distributors, SF-126, 1988 (Box 4)
- Austin, William A., Commit The Sins, Newsstand Library, U 165, 1961 (Box 2)
- Bannon, A., Odd Girl Out, Fawcett Pub., 653, 1957 (Box 1)
- Bannon, Ann, Odd Girl Out, Fawcett Pub., S 965, 1957 (Box 1)
- Bannon, Ann, Women In The Shadows, Fawcett Pub., S 919, 1959 (Box 1)
- Bannon, Ann, I Am A Woman (Signed By Author), Fawcett Publications, T2227, 1959 (Box 4)
- Barstead, Harry, Love Me!, Private Edition, PE 305, 1965 (Box 2)
- Bellaugh, James, The Hollow Venus, Brandon House, 939, 1965 (Box 1)
- Bennett, Adrian, My Lovely Adele, Avon Books, G-1101, 1962 (Box 4)
- Boycott, Billie, No Man's Land, Arthur H. Stockwell, -0-, 1978 (Box 2)
- Britain, Sloane, Meet Marilyn, Tower, 52, 1960 (Box 3)
- Britain, Sloane, Meet Marilyn, Tower, F 284, 1960 (Box 3)
- Brown, Carter, The Deadly Kitten, New American Library, D 3345, 1967 (Box 2)
- Brown, Wenzell, Women of Evil, Monarch Books, 293, 1963 (Box 4)
- Burns, Vincent E., Female Convict, Pyramid, 58, 1952 (Box 2)
- Carson, Dave, Sex III, Universal Publishing, Beacon Books, B 445F, 1961 (Box 5)
- Cassel, Lucas (also Norton, Gene), Wet, Wild and Wonderful (also Anything for Kicks), Midwood Enterprises, 34-888, 1967 (Box 4)
- Christian, Paula, Edge of Twilight,Fawcett Publications, Crest Books, S267, 1959 (Box 5)
- Christian, Paula, Love Is Where You Find It, Hearst Corporation, Avon Book, G-1091, 1961 (Box 5)
- Christian, Paula, The Other Side of Desire, Paperback Library, 52-833, 1965 (Box 4)
- Clanton, Carol, Gay Interlude, Tower, F 95, 1961 (Box 3)
- Clements, Mark, Teacher's Pet, Midwood Enterprises, F333, 1963 (Box 4)
- Craig, Saxon, College Sex Queans, Private Edition, Raven Books, RB 714, 1963 (Box 5)
- Curson, Stanley, Counterfeit Lesbian, Brandon House Book, 623, 1963 (Box 5)
- de Granamour, A., Three More Painful Years, Consolidated Publishing, GP 128, 1969 (Box 4)
- Dean, Ralph, Anything Goes, Bedside Books, BB 825, 1959 (Box 1)
- Dean, Ralph, One Kind of Woman, Universal Publishing, S95154, 1959 (Box 4)
- des Cars, Guy, The Damned One, Pyramid, G 224, 1956 (Box 2)
- Douglas, Craig, Black Silk Dyke, Nite Lite Books, NL 206, 1964 (Box 4)
- Du Val, Pierre, French Dressing, Connoisseur Publications, FN 111, 1964 (Box 1)
- Dumont, Jessie, Made in Hell, Lancer Books, 72-647, 1962 (Box 4)
- Ellis, John, Gay Scene, Tower, F 169, 1962 (Box 3)
- Emery, Carol, Queer Affair, Universal, B 135, 1957 (Box 3)
- Evans, Lesley, Strange Are The Ways Of Love, Fawcett Pub., S 336, 1959 (Box 2)
- Fletcher, Tony, Odd Man Out, After Hours, AH 111, 1964 (Box 1)
- Flora, Fletcher, Strange Sisters, Lion Books, 215, 1954 (Box 2)
- Flora, Fletcher, Whisper Of Love, Pyramid, F-691, 1955 (Box 2)
- Flora, Fletcher, Whisper Of Love, Pyramid, G 384, 1955 (Box 2)
- Golightly, Bonnie, The Shades Of Evil, Hillman Books, 162, 1960 (Box 2)
- Gordon, Diane, Lesbian Girls, Monogram Publications, XB-112, 1971 (Box 4)
- Gray, Stella, Abnormals Anonymous, National Library Books, NLB-106, 1964 (Box 2)
- Hamilton, Greg, The Strange One, Tower Publications, Midwood Books, 32-564, 1965 (Box 5)
- Hanson, Doris, The Intimate Story Of A Lesbian, L. S. Publications, 719, 1965 (Box 2)
- Hardin, Charles, Notes From The Fringe, M T Publishers, NL 1070, 1969 (Box 2)
- Hastings, March, The Outcasts, Tower, F 134, 1961 (Box 3)
- Hastings, March, By Flesh Alone, Tower, F 208, 1962 (Box 3)
- Holk, Agnette, Strange Friends, Pyramid Books, R-863, 1955 (Box 4)
- Holk, Agnette, Strange Friends, Almat Publishing, Pyramid Books, G170, 1955 (Box 5)
- Holliday, Don, Sin School, Tower, 25, 1959 (Box 2)
- Howard, T. J., The Fourth Sex, Brandon House, 1028, 1966 (Box 1)
- Jannsen, Rick, A Loving Son, Tiburon House Publishing Co., RWS/201, 1972 (Box 4)
- Kemp, Kimberly, Party Time, Tower Publications, Midwood Books, 32-426, 1964 (Box 5)
- Kent, Justin, Mavis, Universal, B 695, 1953 (Box 3)
- Kersh, Gerald, Prelude To A Certain Midnight, Lion Books, 98, 1947 (Box 2)
- Koby, Dale, Perverted Wife, Art Enterprises, Inc., Epic Original, 136, 1962 (Box 5)
- Lord, Sheldon, 69 Barrow Street, Tower, 24, 1959 (Box 2)
- Lord, Sheldon, A Strange Kind Of Love, Tower, 9, 1959 (Box 2)
- Lord, Sheldon, 21 Gay Street, Tower, 55, 1960 (Box 3)
- Lord, Sheldon, A Woman Must Love, Tower, 33, 1960 (Box 3)
- Lord, Sheldon, Candy, Tower, 40, 1960 (Box 3)
- Lord, Sheldon, Of Shame And Joy, Tower, 29, 1960 (Box 3)
- Lord, Sheldon, Of Shame And Joy, Tower Publications, Midwood Books, 29, 1960 (Box 5)
- Lord, Sheldon, Of Shame And Joy, Tower, F 121, 1961 (Box 3)
- Lord, Sheldon, The Third Way, Universal, B 790, 1962 (Box 3)
- Lord, Sheldon, The Sisterhood, Universal, S 95189, 1963 (Box 3)
- Lucchesi, Aldo, Strange Breed, Tower, 44, 1960 (Box 3)
- March, Lisa, "Her And She And Him...", Audubon Books, 441-32750, 1970 (Box 1)
- Mark, Edwina, My Sister, My Beloved, Berkley, G-141, 1955 (Box 1)
- Mark, Edwina, My Sister, My Beloved, Berkley Publishing, G-44, 1955 (Box 5)
- Marr, Reed, Women Without Men, Fawcett Pub., 638, 1957 (Box 1)
- Marshe, Richard, A Woman Called Desire, Berkley, G-236, 1950 (Box 1)
- Mayo, Dallas, When Lights Are Low, Tower Publications, Midwood Books, F315, 1963 (Box 5)
- Mayo, Dallas, Pretty Puppet, Tower Publications, Midwood Books, F371, 1964 (Box 5)
- Mayo, Dallas, Pagan Summer, Tower Publications, Midwood Books, 32-465, 1965 (Box 5)
- Michaels, Rea, Naked in the Night, Domino Books, 82-103, 1965 (Box 4)
- Miller, Marcus, The Golden Dyke, Corinth Publications, LB 1217, 1967 (Box 1)
- Moore, Hal R., Odd Girl, Designs Publishing Corporation, Intimate Novels, 56, 1954 (Box 5)
- Murry, P., A Dandy, Pendulum Books, -0-, 1968 (Box 2)
- Napier, Dominique, Never Love A Man, Universal Publishing, B511F, 1962 (Box 4)
- Nemec, John, Was She A Dyke?, Art Enterprises Inc., I 727, 1963 (Box 4)
- Packer, Vin, Spring Fire, Fawcett Pub., 398, 1952 (Box 1)
- Packer, Vin, The Evil Friendship, Fawcett Pub., S 797, 1958 (Box 1)
- Packer, Vin, The Evil Friendship, Fawcett Pub., 520-00299, 1958 (Box 2)
- Pardo, Edyie, Lesbian Journal: Fran's Love of a Young Girl, American Art Enterprises, LF-116, 1985 (Box 4)
- Parish, Cal, Tortured Triangle, Triumph News Co., TNC 301, 1967 (Box 3)
- Pratt, Theodore, The Tormented, Fawcett Pub., S 933, 1950 (Box 1)
- Pritchard, Janet Warped Women, Universal Publishing, Beacon Books, B 121, 1956 (Box 5)
- Rico, Don, The Unmarried Ones, Universal, B 713, 1964 (Box 3)
- Russo, Paul V., This Yielding Flesh, Tower Publications, Midwood Books, 94, 1961 (Box 5)
- Salem, Randy, Chris, Universal, B 223, 1959 (Box 3)
- Salem, Randy, Tender Torment, Tower Publications, Midwood Books, F172, 1962 (Box 5)
- Sherwood, Paula, Rubdown, Wee Hours, WH 540, 1967 (Box 4)
- Shields, Frank, The Gay Sinners, P. E. C., N 138, 1966 (Box 2)
- Simon, George, Girls Without Men, Universal Publishing, S75142, 1964 (Box 4)
- Smith, Artemis, The Third Sex, Beacon, B268, 1959 (Box 3)
- Smith, Artemis, This Bed We Made, Monarch Books, 182, 1961 (Box 2)
- Smith, Barry, Good Night Sweet Dyke, All Star Books, AS 61, 1965 (Box 1)
- Swados, Felice, House of Fury, Avon Books, 430, 1941 (Box 4)
- Taylor, Valerie, Whisper Their Love, Fawcett Pub., 187, 1957 (Box 2)
- Thomas, Lee, Mask Of Lesbos, Universal, B 627, 1963 (Box 3)
- Thompson, Sharon L., Reaper Of Wild Oats, Caravalle Books, 092-00863, 1968 (Box 1)
- Torres, Tereska, Women's Barracks, World Dist., 1116, 1950 (Box 3)
- Tryon, Mark, Of G-Strings and Strippers, Beacon Books, B273, 1953 (Box 4)
- Vail, Ann, Diary Of A Lesbian, Triumph News Co., TNC 103, 1967 (Box 3)
- Vail, Ann, The Lesbian, E. L. Publishing Co., CS-34, 1971 (Box 1)
- Vast, Jack, Hush Hush Sweet Harlot, All Star Books, AS 71, 1966 (Box 1)
- Verel, Shirley, The Dark Side of Venus, Bantam Books, F2434, 1962 (Box 4)
- Wade, Carlson, The Troubled Sex, Universal, E 105F, 1961 (Box 3)
- Weiss, Joe, Anything Goes, Bedside Books, BB 825, 1959 (Box 1)
- West, Edwin, Strange Affair, Monarch Books, 232, 1962 (Box 5)
- Wilde, Rita, Two-Way Street, P. E. C., FL 70, 1970 (Box 2)
- Wilhelm, Gale, We Too Are Drifting, Berkley, G-173, 1935 (Box 1)
- Wilhelm, Gale, No Letters For The Dead, Lion Books, 52, 1936 (Box 2)
- Wilhelm, Gale, No Nice Girl, Pyramid, G 440, 1936 (Box 2)
- Wilhelm, Gale, Paula, Lion Books, LB 115, 1936 (Box 2)
- Williams, Isabel, Hellcat, Dell, 521, 1934 (Box 1)
- Willow, Peter, 3 Way Split, After Hours, AH 117, 1965 (Box 1)
- Wilson, Barbara, The Velvet Embrace, Lancer Books, 72-949, 1965 (Box 3)